RADHIKA LELE

Front End Web Developer

♥ Brampton,Ontario ☆ Extra Field

SUMMARY

A Front End Developer with a passion for creating responsive and accessible web applications using JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS, and SCSS. With a strong foundation in programming, backed by two years of experience in customer service and teaching, I possess a unique blend of technical expertise and interpersonal skills. I am committed to creating engaging and user-friendly experiences for website visitors, and have a keen eye for design and user experience.

PROJECTS

Multi-page Site

https://glittering-lily-61b3f1.netlify.app https://github.com/Radhika-Lele/RadhikaLeleProjectOne Translated static design images into functional, responsive website using HTML, CSS and SCSS

EDUCATION

Web Development Immersive Bootcamp Certificate

Juno College of Technology, Toronto, ON

= 03/2023 - 06/2023

Master of Engineering in Electronics and Telecommunication Engineering

University of Mumbai,India

= 08/2015 - 10/2017

Bachelor of Engineering in Electrical and Electronics Engineering

Amravati University, India

m 08/2010 - 06/2014

SKILLS

HTML	CSS	JavaScript		React
SCSS	Git & Git-Hub		Web Accessibility	
Restful APIs				

EXPERIENCE

Customer Service Sales Representative

Alorica

= 05/2019 - 08/2020 Montral, Quebec

- Contacted potential customers to capitalize on new sale, cross-sale and up-sale opportunities
- Consistently exceeding sales targets by 80%, building strong relationships with clients, and effectively communicating the value of our products and services

Customer Service Representative

CURO Financial Technologies

- Resolved customer complaints and inquiries with a 95% satisfaction rating, leading to increased customer retention and loyalty
- Developed strong relationship with customers, resulting in an 89% customer retention rate using modern negotiation tactics.
- Managed an average of 50+ customer inquires per day, ensuring all issues were resolved in a timely and satisfactory manner

Teaching Assistant

Thakur College of Engineering and Technology (TCET)

= 07/2016 - 06/2017

Mumbai,India

- Taught labs and conducted workshops for 120 undergraduate and graduate students of the Electronics Engineering division
- Designed and delivered engaging presentations that have helped students understand complex engineering concepts in a clear and concise manner.

Powered by CV Enhancy